This is Runwiser.
It turns repeated agent work into reusable workflow assets, with proof attached.
The landing page leads with the operating model.
Runs create evidence, gates check quality, and only verified work moves forward.
This is not loose multi-agent parallelism.
Specialized roles hand work across bounded review and verification steps.
The wiki also shows up on the landing page as a public knowledge surface.
That makes the system feel browsable instead of hidden.
Then the live wiki service makes that idea concrete.
You can open the catalog, enter a page, and browse promoted workflow knowledge directly.
The repository mirrors the same lifecycle.
Architecture documents explain the layers, the boundaries, and where each asset belongs.
The proof is not abstract.
You can see runs, workflows, scripts, knowledge assets, and scenario wrappers living in separate layers inside the repo.
That is the point of Runwiser.
Make agent work measurable, improvable, and reusable by preserving evidence before promotion.